Guide to the Sexuality in Society Ephemera, 1960-2015
Sexuality in Society Ephemera, 1960-2015
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sexuality in society ephemera, 1960-2015
7323
4.9 cubic feet
Flyers, brochures, broadsides, newsletters, buttons, bumper stickers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains materials relating to sexual politics and the culture of groups defined by sexuality. Includes materials collected on the campus of Cornell University and from a wide range of U.S. and international cities.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Broadsides publicizing events, films, and exhibits, and flyers, brochures, buttons, bumper stickers, card decks, safe sex packets, single issues of newsletters, currency marked "lesbian money" and "gay money," and other materials relating to sexual politics and the culture of groups defined by sexuality. Primarily includes materials handed out at marches, rallies, parades, lectures, conferences, picnics, women's bookstores, and entertainment shows by, for, or about lesbians, gay men, and bisexuals, from the 1980s on. Homophobia and responses to acts of homophobia are also documented. Also includes an erotic deck of cards with photographs of nude women and men engaged mostly in heterosexual and group sex scenes, circa 1960s.
Events documented include an October 12, 1992, ACT UP demonstration in D.C.; the 1992 Atlanta Pride March; the 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Rights and Liberation; the 1994 Stonewall 25 Parade; and Toshi Reagon's and Sara Cytron's performances as part of the 150th Anniversary of the Seneca Falls Women's Rights Convention, July 1998. Also included are posters announcing events at CLAGS, the Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies at the City University of New York. N.Y. Representative Anthony Weiner's May 2011 sexting scandal prompted the marketing of a Weiner action figure, one of which is in this collection.
Material collected at San Francisco Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration, June 30, 1991, includes documentation of transvestites and Asian-Americans.
Includes ephemera from a wide range of U.S. cities, including Flint and Ann Arbor, Michigan; New Hope, Pennsylvania; Cincinnati; Chicago; Charlotte; Oklahoma; Houston; Madison, Wisconsin; New York, Rochester, Syracuse, Trumansburg, and Ithaca, New York; and Santa Cruz, San Diego, and Sacramento, California.
Also, photocopies of Polish gay material, including INACZEJI, which has an article on the first gay pride celebration in Poland, and lesbian and gay ephemera from places including Montreal, Winnepeg, Vancouver, and Saskatchewan, Canada; Tokyo, Japan; Austria; Sydney, Australia; and Germany.
Art-related work includes New York City bus posters on AIDS; a signed copy of Audre Lorde's poem "Sisters in Arms"; publicity for artist Jan Phillips; AIDS benefit posters from the Austin Festival of Dance; and two posters acquired by Cornell's Johnson Museum of Art for its recognition of the Day Without Art, December 1, 1998; t-shirts from 1993 March on Washington and The L Word (donated by Nancy Law) and a stuffed figure representing HIV.
A rainbow button with a buck, labeled "Bucks M.C. [Motorcycle Club] Present 2003 Santa Saturday," comes from an event on Saturday, November 29 at Cartwheel's Nightclub in New Hope, Pennsylvania. "Santa Saturday" is an annual event, at which bears from all over the East Coast gather for fun and as a charity benefit to raise money for holiday toys for underprivileged children. The event typically starts at 1:00 in the afternoon and goes throughout the day, featuring drag shows and an auction.
Responses to homophobia include labels made to affix to copies of Reader's Guide warning of the exclusion of lesbian and gay writing. These labels were distributed at a mid-winter conference of the American Library Association held in San Antonio in January 1992. The collection also contains posters that appeared on the Cornell University campus on February 20, 1995, in response to Prof. Jim Aist's offer to provide Christian information and counseling to those seeking to "cure" their homosexuality.
Additional buttons cover topics such as AIDS, bisexuality, lesbianism, gay rights, and opposition to war and racism.
Unique set of cardboard cutouts/magnets featuring Moe from Alison Bechdel’s cartoon strip Dykes to Watch out For and accessories.
Memorabilia (including stickers, flyers and a small pride flag) collected at San Francisco LGBT pride parade on June 28, 2015 and Paris pride parade.
SUBJECTS
Names:
City University of New York. Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies.; March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation, 1993: Washington, D.C.; Lorde, Audre.; Phillips, Jan.; Reagon, Toshi.; Cytron, Sara.
Subjects:
Bears (Gay culture)--Pennsylvania.; Bisexuality--United States.; Demonstrations--United States.; Gay liberation movement--United States.; Gay liberation movement--Poland.; Gay men--United States--Political activity.; Gay men--United States--Societies and clubs.; Gay men--United States--Social life and customs.; Gay motorcycle clubs--Pennsylvania.; Gays--Quebec--Montreal.; Gays--United States.; Gays' writings, American.; Group sex--United States.; Heterosexuals--United States.; Homophobia.; Lesbians--Quebec--Montreal.; Lesbians--United States--Political activity.; Lesbians--United States--Societies and clubs.; Lesbians--United States--Social life and customs.; Safe sex in AIDS prevention--United States.; Transvestites--United States--Political activity.; Vietnamese-Americans.
Places:
Provincetown (Mass.)--Social life and customs.; New York (N.Y.)--Social life and customs.; Rochester (N.Y.)--Social life and customs.; Oklahoma--Social life and customs.; Madison (Wis.)--Social life and customs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Broadsides.; Brochures.; Ephemera.; Erotica.; Buttons (information artifacts).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Relevant items may be found in Regional History Broadsides, #6629, Cornell University Broadsides, #37-7-3406, and in collections related to the Gay Games and Stonewall 25.
CONTAINER LIST
- "Gay Money", 1987; San Francisco, California (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Handouts from Womencrafts, Gabriel's, and 4th of July Parade, 1989; Provincetown, Massachusetts, July 4th weekend, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Organizations' flyers, brochures, newsletters, lesbian and Gay money, Tim Mains flyers, 1989; Rochester, New York, Annual Gay Picnic, July 16, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Flyers, newspaper articles, correspondence with university concerning Gay Center, 1981-1982; Oklahoma State University (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bulletins, newsletters, miscellany, 1981-1982; Oklahoma (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Homemade wrapper from a bar of Lilli's Lesbian Love Chocolate, Sold during the first meetings of East and West German feminists upon the opening of the Berlin Wall in Berlin, Germany (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Finger Lakes Grassroots Festival Program - "Supporting the Fight Against AIDS", July 16-19, 1992; Trumansburg, New York (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Card from San Francisco Pride Parade, flyer from Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, June 1992; San Francisco, California (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Syracuse University Pride Celebration Program, 1984; Syracuse, New York (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fundraising flyer, Stillwater, Oklahoma (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Flyers from Califia Community, Pandora's Box, Feminist Writers' Guild, West Coast Women's Music and Cultural Festival, 1981; California (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Announcement posted in lobby of National Lesbian Conference entitled "Dykes with Dough", April 24-28, 1991; Atlanta, Georgia (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Gay Men's Health Crisis: Safe Sex Comix, New York City, New York (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Miscellany (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "Sodomy Night" flyer, 1991; Austin, Texas (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Gay Atheists brochure (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Lesbian and Gay alumni flyer, Ithaca, New York (Box 1, Folder 18)
- "Romanovsky and Phillips and Alix Dobkin in concert", October 12, 1990; Cornell University, Ithaca, New York (Box 1, Folder 19)
- "International Mr. Leather" flyers and brochures; National March on Washington videotape order forms, 1987; Chicago, Illinois, May 22-25, 1987; Washington, D.C., October 11, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Condom from Gannett Health Services, Cornell University; DYKE label; lesbian/gay/bisexual checks order form, Robert Ames(?) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Tarot cards (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Gay Name Game by Tom Wilson, 1979; 12" phonodisc (Box 2)
- Walls to Roses, Songs of Changing Men, 1979; 12" phonodisc (Box 2)
- Please Tip Your Waitress by Willie Sordill, 1980; 12" phonodisc (Box 2)
- Short Eyes by Curtis Mayfield, 1977; 12" phonodisc (Box 2)
- Workers World, The National Alliance, from Gay Pride March, June 25, 1989; New York City, New York (Box 2)
- Safe sex packet, June 25, 1989; New York City, New York, Gay Pride March (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Button from 4th of July parade, July 4, 1989; Provincetown, Massachusetts (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Safe sex packet, Tim Mains bumper sticker, July 16, 1989; Rochester, New York, Annual Gay Picnic (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous gay buttons, fake money, key chains (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Safe sex packet from a workshop on Lesbians and Safe Sex, April 12-14, 1991; Austin, Texas, Texas Lesbian Conference (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Flyer announcing Women's History Week, March 2-8, 1986; Possibly the first Women's History Week Celebration devoted to Lesbian History, Madison, Wisconsin (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Cards, flyers, advertisements, ACT UP flyers, June 25, 1989; New York City, New York, Gay Pride March Parade (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The Brazen Hussy Rag, Our Time, 1982-1983; Oklahoma (Box 4, Folder 3)
- "Dyke, A Quarterly, First Anniversary Issue, 1976-77", 1976-1977; Poster (Box 5)
- "March on Washington, October 11, 1987", advertisement for the Official March on Washington videotape, 1987; Poster (Box 5)
- International Lesbian and Gay Association, 11th Annual Conference, July 16-22, 1989, Vienna, Austria, 1989; Poster (Box 5)
- "New York City Pride and History Month, June 1989", 1989; Poster (2 copies) (Box 5)
- "Our Gang," announcing the First Annual Gay Junior Prom, The Class Event of 1982, 1982; Poster (Box 5)
- "The Divine Androgyne According to Purusha," advertisement for a book by Purusha Androgyne Larkin, San Diego, California, 1981; Poster (2 copies) (Box 5)
- "Gay Press Association Convention in Philadelphia April 29-May 1, 1983", Northeast Region Bulletin, April, 1983, 1983; Poster (Box 5)
- "The Gay and Lesbian Community and Services Center" announcing upcoming events, Hollywood, California, Poster (Box 5)
- "Fourth Annual Gay Musical Celebration," Golden Gate Performing Arts, San Francisco, California, June 1983, 1983; Poster (Box 5)
- "Open Lines," announcing upcoming poetry readings, New York City, Poster (Box 5)
- "Sweat," advertisement for the Chelsea Gym for Men, New York City, Poster (Box 5)
- "Sex, Politics, and The Law: Lesbians and Gay Men Take the Offensive," New York University, February 22, 1986; Flyer (Box 5)
- "Behind The Smile: Bruce Buchy Sings," Jan Wallman's Restaurant, New York City, 1982; Flyer (Box 5)
- "International Leather Man 1987," Chicago, Illinois, May 22-25, 1987, 1987; Poster (2 copies) (Box 5)
- Greek Lesbian and Gay Liberation, "Our Self-Ruling Movement is Waiting For You", Poster (Box 5)
- "Gay Community News" t-shirt, 1984 (Box 6)
- "National March on Washington" t-shirt, October 11, 1987; Washington, D.C. (Box 6)
- "Cornell Celebrates National Condom Week" t-shirt; Pillow case banner entitled, "Our Bodies, Our Choice," made by local activists Paisley Currah and Shannon Minter, circa 1990; Ithaca, New York, Gannett Health Center, 1990 (Box 6)
- Larry Bothwell collected ephemera, Primarily regarding gays and religion (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- "SIDA: el miedo es no saber", Bumper sticker (Box 7, Folder 3)
- National Coming Out Day packets, 1988; Ordering information/invoice (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Gay directory - Key West, Florida, circa 1970s (Box 7, Folder 5)
- New York City Lesbian and Gay Pride Week program, 1979; New York, New York (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Directory of the River City Business Association, 1980; Sacramento, California (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Gay Valentine's Day card, 1960s? (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Town Squire Men's Clothing catalogue, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "Homophile: Real Answers Not Red Ribbons" pamphlet, 1992; Washington, D.C. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Bag from "Q Notes", Charlotte, North Carolina. From Mark Handel. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous ephemera from Pride Festivals, 1992-1995; North Carolina. From Mark Handel. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous ephemera from Pride Festival, 1996; Charlotte, North Carolina. From Mark Handel. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- "AIDS Walk New York Sunday May 2, 1993" t-shirt, 1993; New York, New York. From Mark Handel. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "AIDS Walk New York Volunteer" t-shirt, 1993; New York, New York. From Mark Handel. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous ephemera from the Display of the AIDS Memorial Quilt, 1996; Washington, D.C. From Michael Busch. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous buttons (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Buttons covering topics such as AIDS, bisexuality, lesbianism, gay rights, and opposition to war and racism, Lambda Report, Undo Amendment 2, Equal Protection Portland, No on 9. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Program guide and miscellaneous collections from March on Washington, 1993; Washington, D.C. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous ephemera from March on Washington, 1993; Washington, D.C. (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
- One wrapped and one unwrapped survey packet entitled: "This Time We Will Be Counted", 1993; Washington, D.C. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Film and music festival programs, 1982-1990; San Francisco, California (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Freedom banquet, film and music festival, and Gay San Diego contest programs, 1982-1983; San Diego, California (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 8th Annual Walk for Life program, 1995; Austin, Texas (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Gay Pride Parade and Festival program, 1980; Los Angeles, California (Box 11, Folder 4)
- 14th Annual Boston Lesbian and Gay Pride Celebration Calendar of Events, 1984; Boston, Massachusetts (Box 11, Folder 5)
- National Reno Gay Rodeo Program, 1982; Reno, Nevada (Box 11, Folder 6)
- The Advocate Groovy Guy programs, 1972-1973; Hollywood, California (Box 11, Folder 7)
- "The First National Lesbian and Gay Writers Conference" sponsored by the OUT/LOOK Foundation, 1990; Out Write (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Human Rights Campaign Fund Celebration (1985) and film festival programs, 1984-1989; New York, New York (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Exhibit catalogue: "Prejudice and Pride: The New York City Lesbian and Gay Community", 1988; New York, New York (Box 11, Folder 10)
- International Lesbian and Gay Freedom Day Program, 1983; San Francisco, California (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Assorted pamphlets, flyers, and brochures relating to the prevention, diagnosis, and treatment of AIDS and other sexually transmitted diseases, 1992; Quebec, Montreal. From Brenda Marston. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Collected newsletters and periodicals, 1992; Quebec, Montreal. From Brenda Marston. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Flyers, advertisements, brochures, and tourist guides produced by feminist and lesbian/gay/bisexual businesses and organizations, 1992; Quebec, Montreal. From Brenda Marston. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Toronto Lambda Business Council Directory of Gay Business Gaydays Souvenir Programme, 1978; Toronto, Ontario (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Calendar of erotic lesbian photographs entitled: "Pandora's Box: 1995 Queer Women's Safer Sex Calendar; A Benefit for the Santa Cruz AIDS Project", 1995; Santa Cruz, California. From Dana Luciano. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Calendar of erotic lesbian photographs entitled: "Jamie Griffiths 1996 Calendar", 1995; San Francisco, California. From Dana Luciano. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Dignity Flint brochure, circa 1980; Flint, Michigan (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Cincinnati Men's Network brochure, circa 1980s; Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Flyer advertising "Big Daddy's" bar, 1973; Buffalo, New York (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Gay and Lesbian Support Services brochure/newsletter, circa 1981; Saskatchewan, Canada (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Program from "Emerging Voices: A Conference on Gay and Lesbian Studies for Undergraduate and Graduate Students", November 10-11, 1995; Also a revised version of a paper given by Vinh Quoc Nguyen entitled "Dynamics of Displacement in Representations of Male Homosexual Desire in Modern Vietnamese Literature". Princeton, New Jersey. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Photocopy of a program from "Envisioning and Building Our Own Community: Vietnamese Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Conference and Celebration", September 2-4, 1994; San Jose, California (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Photocopy of a program from a performance entitled "ExtravaGapa...Cultural Images" (GAPA signifies Gay Asian Pacific Alliance), December 2, 1990; Fort Mason, California? (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Paper by Professor Breslin entitled "Yellow and Pink All Over: issues and Identities of Gay Vietnamese American Men", May 16, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Photocopy of program from "Fourth Annual Vietnamese Queer Conference", 1996; San Francisco, California (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Notes from panel discussion led by Vinh Quoc Nguyen at "49th Annual AAS Meeting" entitled "Constructing the Indochinese Body", March 15, 1997; Chicago, Illinois (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Photocopies of newsletters from the Gay Vietnamese Alliance including the "GV Voice", 1996; California (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Three photocopied newsletters: VietNow, VN: The Voice of Vietnamese Lesbians and Gays, and K'y Túc Xá, 1981, 1993, Undated; California (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Program from "Crystal Boys" presented by the Adams Chinese Theatre Series for the Harvard Gay and Lesbian Caucus Night, April 26, 1997; Cambridge, Massachusetts (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Program from "Dem Ha Vang/Yellow Summer Night: A Vietnamese Cultural Show" presented by Doi Dien Magazine, July 4, 1993; San Jose, California (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Newspaper clippings including a photocopied article from the Daily Bruin (UCLA) entitled "Bisexual Cadet Faces Discharge", January 1996; Los Angeles, California (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Photocopy of article in the Orange County Register entitled "When Worlds Collide: Vietnamese gays fight intense pressure from a traditional culture", May 2, 1996; Orange County, California (Box 13, Folder 19)
- William F. Gratz, James A. Bruno wedding invitation, October 12, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Lesbian Avengers poster: "Dykes Fight Back", 1994; New York, New York. From Dana Luciano. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Poster advertising panel on "AIDS in Central Virginia: The Medical and Legal Future", Virginia (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Printed poem from Christopher Street Liberation Day on June 28, 1970, 1970; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Leaflet printed by Lesbians Against Police Violence in response to May 21st "Twinkie Riots" following Dan White's case, circa 1979; Oakland, California (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Program/brochure from March on Washington, 1987; Washington, D.C. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Program from conference entitled "Lesbian Solidarity '82", 1982; San Diego, California (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Pamphlet entitled "Religion is the Problem not the Answer" and flyers published by the Gay Atheist League of America (GALA), 1986; San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Program from "Threshold of the Future" Convention sponsored by the Daughters of Bilitis, 1964; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Pamphlet entitled "About Coming Out" published by Gays for Equality, circa 1980; Winnipeg, Manitoba (Box 15, Folder 7)
- New Pacific Academy for Lesbian and Gay Community Service and Activism information packet, 1990; San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Conference program from "AIDS: Improving the Odds" sponsored by the Columbia Gay Health Advocacy Project, 1989; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Fundraising and other letters to congregants of Beth Chayim Chadashim, 1981-83; Los Angeles, California (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Program and other material from Gaylaxicon IV Convention, 1991; Tewskbury, Massachusetts (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Gay and Lesbian Guide to Provincetown, brochure listing local women-owned businesses, brochure for Gabriel's women's guest house collected over Memorial Day weekend, 1997; Provincetown, Massachusetts. From Amanda Littauer. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Empire State Pride Agenda election flyer, 1996; New York State (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Map of gay and lesbian tourist attractions in Miami and Miami Beach published by Columbia Fun Maps, 1997; Miami, Florida (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Human Rights Campaign "party pack" from April 30th "Ellen" Coming Day House Party and flyer for local party sponsored by LBQ (Lesbian Bisexual Questioning Women), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Human Rights Campaign "party pack" video tape from April 30th "Ellen" Coming Out Day House Party sponsored locally by LBQ, 1997; Ithaca, New York (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Montréal Gay Map, 1985; Montréal, Québec (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Pamphlet entitled "Love and Let Love"; flyer entitled "Manitoba Gay Directory", late 1970s; Winnipeg, Manitoba (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 1972 Gay Pride Special of Christopher Street West; Gay and Lesbian Pride week Calendar, June 1978; "Pride Guide '83", 1972, 1978, 1983; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Guide to Houston Gay and Lesbian Pride Week, 1987; Houston, Texas (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Los Angeles Times article entitled "Monitoring the Media: Activist Alliance Exercises Clout in Fighting Anti-Gay Images", 1990; Los Angeles, California (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Various informational packets from G.R.O.W., including a catalog entitled "Feminist Book Mart", 1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Pamphlet from the National Gay Rights Advocates (NGRA) entitled "AIDS, Civil Rights and the Public Health: America's Leaders Speak Out", 1988; San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 23)
- "Nutritional Guidelines for persons with HIV infection" pamphlet, printed by HealthGain, 1994; San Clemente, California (Box 15, Folder 24)
- "Caring for Someone With AIDS" pamphlet, printed by the the CDC (Center for Disease Control), 1991; Washington, D.C. (Box 15, Folder 25)
- HIV In America: A Report by the National Association of People with AIDS, 1992; Washington, D.C. (Box 15, Folder 26)
- WNBA player facts sheet, includes pictures of players, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Booklet with information on the National AIDS Memorial Grove in Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Information About AIDS for the Columbia Community, printed by Columbia University Health Services, 1986; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Parents of Gays Pamphlet printed to help parents of gays, includes contact information for local services and reading lists, 1977; Washington, D.C. (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Gay Men and STDS Pamphlet printed by the New York State Department of Health, 1978; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 31)
- "About Our Children" pamphlet printed by PFLAG, 1978; Contains information in 4 languages other than English. Los Angeles, California. (Box 15, Folder 32)
- "Homosexuality: your questions answered" pamphlet printed by Camp NSW, 1977; Sydney, Australia (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Publication of G.R.O.W., a lesbian organization of the Genesee Valley Area, Rochester, New York (Box 15, Folder 34)
- "Gay Pride and the conomic crisis" informational leaflet, 1975; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Program from "The Future of the Queer Past: A Transnational History Conference" held at the University of Chicago, September 14-17, 2000; Chicago, Illinois (Box 15, Folder 36)